A Guide to the Charles Uht photographs FA103
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Nelson A. Rockefeller (NAR), I
  - Slides, Art A-Z, I_5
    - Weiss - Attack on the Realm (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Weiss - The Farm, after van Gogh (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Winter - Approaching (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous - Jewelry (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous - Prattsville Green (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous - Home Interior (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous - Bodhisattva (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Unidentified (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Unidentified/Artifact (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Glarner Installation 812 Fifth Avenue Prints (Box 20)
    - Kykuit Aerials Prints (Box 21)
  - Printed Material, I_7
    - Memorial Service Program for Michael C. Rockefeller, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 69)
    - Memorial Service Program for Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 69)
    - Memorial Service Program for Wallace K. Harrison (Box 23, Folder 69)
    - Herald Tribune Article, "Art and the Rockefellers", 1959 April 5 (Box 23, Folder 69)
    - Newspaper Article, JDR 3rd (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - 35mm, Primitive Art Exhibit Installation, I_6
    - 35mm, Primitive Art Exhibit Installation (Box 22)
- Laurance S. Rockefeller (LSR), II
  - 4x5, Negatives, Artwork, II_1_2_1
    - Artwork (Box 24)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Commemorative Plaques and Medals, II_1_2_2
    - Commemorative Plaques and Medals (Box 24)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Jewelry, II_1_2_3
    - Jewelry (Box 24)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Model Airplane collection, II_1_2_4
    - Model Airplane collection (Box 24)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Museum Objects, II_1_2_5
    - Museum Objects (Box 24)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Rockefeller family, II_1_2_6
    - Rockefeller family (Box 24)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Woodstock, VT, II_1_2_7
    - Interiors (Box 24)
    - Exteriors (Box 24)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Miscellaneous, II_1_2_8
    - Miscellaneous (with art objects) (Box 24)
  - 4x5, Prints, Model Airplane collection, II_1_3_1
    - Model Airplane collection (Box 24)
  - 4x5, Prints, Miscellaneous, II_1_3_2
    - Miscellaneous (Box 24)
  - 5x7, Negatives, II_2_2
    - Woodstock, VT (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - 8x10, Transparencies, II_3_1
    - History of Woodstock, VT (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - 8x10, Negatives, II_3_2
    - Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - 8x10, Prints, Model Airplane collection, II_3_3_1
    - Model Airplane collection (Box 25, Folder 73-74)
  - 8x10, Prints, Woodstock, VT, II_3_3_2
    - Woodstock, VT - Interiors (Box 25, Folder 75-76)
    - Woodstock, VT - Exteriors (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - 8x10, Prints, Museum Objects, II_3_3_3
    - Museum Objects - Figurines (Box 25, Folder 78)
    - Museum Objects - Jewelry (Box 25, Folder 78)
    - Museum Objects - Silver (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - 8x10, Prints, Miscellaneous, II_3_3_4
    - Portrait of Laura Spelman Rockefeller (Box 25, Folder 80)
    - Painting (Box 25, Folder 80)
    - Prayer of St. Francis (Box 25, Folder 80)
  - 8x10, Prints, Woodstock, VT, II_4_3
    - Woodstock, VT - Interiors (Box 26)
- David Rockefeller (DR), III
  - 4x5, Transparencies, Art A-Z, III_1_1_1
    - Burchfield, Charles Ephraim - House with Tower (1927-49) [2/93] (Box 27)
    - Davis, Stuart - Still Life with Man (1923) [2/124] (Box 27)
    - Porter, Fairfield - The Schooner II (1965) [2/129] (Box 27)
    - French, Leonard - Triptych (1964) [2/227] (Box 27)
    - Rivera, Diego - The Rivals (1931) [2/237] (Box 27)
    - Musavvir, Mu'in - Portrait of the Artist Riza Abbasi [3/286] (Box 27)
    - Penfield, Edward - Poster Calendar (1897) (Box 27)
    - Renoir, Pierre Auguste - Anemones in a Glass Vase [1/172] (Box 27)
    - Signac, Paul - Opus 217?.(1890) [1/177] (Box 27)
  - 4x5, Transparencies, Art Unidentified, III_1_1_2
    - Art - Unidentified (Box 27)
  - 4x5, Transparencies, Oriental Carpets/Rugs, III_1_1_3
    - Oriental Carpets/Rugs (Box 27)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Art A-Z, III_1_2_1
    - Adams, Mark - Sea Rocks (1961) [2/170] (Box 27)
    - Beechey, Sir William - Elizabeth Keene (1790) [1/94] (Box 27)
    - Bonnard, Pierre - Interior (1912-3) [1/226] (Box 27)
    - Boudin, Louis-Eugene - Cliffs At Villerville [1/135] (Box 27)
    - Burchfield, Charles Ephriam - Country Home in Midsummer (1951) [2/94] (Box 27)
    - Burchfield, Charles Ephriam - Going Home (Box 27)
    - Burchfield, Charles Ephriam - House with a Tower (1927-49) [2/93] (Box 27)
    - Campigli, Massimo - The Spanish Steps (1954) [1/322] (Box 27)
    - Carreno, Mario - The Palm Grove (1947) [2/244] (Box 27)
    - Caruso, Bruno - Men Resting (1950's) [1/326] (Box 27)
    - Cezanne, Paul - Les Baigneurs (1896-7) (Box 27)
    - Chagall, Marc - Stained Glass Window, Union Church of Pocantico Hills [1/56] (Box 27)
    - Cross, Henri-Edmond - Group of Pines, Near Cannes (1895) [1/185] (Box 27)
    - Degas, Edgar - Women Seated in Garden (1872-3) [1/131] (Box 27)
    - Demuth, Charles - Zinnias [2/108] (Box 27)
    - Devis, Arthur - Adam Alkinson (1789) [1/92] (Box 27)
    - Devis, Arthur - Ellin Devis (1750-52) [1/90] (Box 27)
    - Duffy, Raoul - Ascot (1937) [1/291] (Box 27)
    - Eilshemius, Louis Michel - Laurel Hill, Arlington, New Jersey (1907) [2/66] (Box 27)
    - Fantin Latour, Henri - Flowers [1/124] (Box 27)
    - Figari, Pedro - The Declaration (1922) [2/233] (Box 27)
    - French, Leonard - Triptych (1964) [2/227] (Box 27)
    - Gauguin, Paul - Maternite (1899) [1/195] (Box 27)
    - Grosz, George - Cape Cod Landscape (1939-42) [2/102] (Box 27)
    - Guys, Constantin - Street Girl, London (1870-3) [1/133] (Box 27)
    - Hickey, Thomas - Major John Osborne (1786) [1/93] (Box 27)
    - Hlito, Alfredo - Painting or Variation II (1959) [2/247] (Box 27)
    - Hopper, Edward - Rich's House, North Truro (1930) [2/90] (Box 27)
    - Ingres, Jean-Auguste-Dominique - Fraulein Ritter (1817) [1/102] (Box 27)
    - Isabey, Jean Baptiste - Portrait of Mme Moreau (1800-4) [1/103] (Box 27)
    - Kandinsky, Wassily - Winter Study with Mountain (1908) [1/317] (Box 27)
    - Lataster, Gerard - Untitled (1952) [2/220] (Box 27)
    - Lemos, Fernando - Ash Composition (1966) [2/249] (Box 27)
    - Lorrain, Claude - Dance Under the Trees (1637) [1/346] (Box 27)
    - Mabe, Manabu - Summer Festival (1967) [2/257] (Box 27)
    - Maze, Paul - Abby, Neva, David, Peggy, Sambo (Box 27)
    - Maze, Paul - Abby, Neva, Peggy, Dick, Sambo (1952) [1/297] (Box 27)
    - Maze, Paul - Beach Scene (Box 27)
    - Maze, Paul - Brooklyn Bridge (Box 27)
    - Maze, Paul - Coronation Coach (Box 27)
    - Maze, Paul - Girl Kneeling (Abby) (1952) [1/297] (Box 27)
    - Maze, Paul - Maine Woods (Box 27)
    - Maze, Paul - Royal Procession (1936) [1/295] (Box 27)
    - Maze, Paul - Seascape, Lady Painting (Box 27)
    - Monet, Claude - The Clump of Grasses [1/147] (Box 27)
    - Monet, Claude - Nympheas (1918-21) [1/141] (Box 27)
    - Dalmatian Motif (1948) [1/324] (Box 27)
    - Obergon, Alejandro - Birth of the Andes (1965) [2/252] (Box 27)
    - Ohtake, Tomie - Painting (1967) [2/254] (Box 27)
    - Pissarro, Camille - Berger et Eglise a Eragny (1889) [1/128] (Box 27)
    - Porzano, Giacomo - Brushes (1959) [1/327] (Box 27)
    - Prendergast, Maurice Brazil - Steps of Santa Maria in Aracoeli, Rome (1898-99) [2/52] (Box 27)
    - Redon, Odilon - Andromeda (Box 27)
    - Redon, Odilon - Flowers [1/208] (Box 27)
    - Schongauer, Martin - Death of the Virgin (1470's) [1/346] (Box 27)
    - de Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri - Aux Ambassadeurs (1894) [1/358] (Box 27)
    - de Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri - Le Jockey (1899) [1/360] (Box 27)
    - de Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri - La Modiste (1899) [1/362] (Box 27)
    - de Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri - Truffier et Moreno, dans Les Femmes Savantes (1893) [1/358] (Box 27)
    - Vespignani, Renzo - Train (1947) [1/328] (Box 27)
    - Vlavianos, Nicolas - Untitled (1967?) [2/260] (Box 27)
    - Van Dogen, Kees - Femme au Chien (1922-23) [1/289] (Box 27)
    - Vasarely, Victor - Ilile (1956-59) [2/216] (Box 27)
    - Vuillard, Edouard - Les Deux Belles-Soeurs (1899) [1/363] (Box 27)
    - Vuillard, Edouard - Jeux d'Enfants (1897) [1/362] (Box 27)
    - Wakabayashi, Kasuo - Light Blue (1966) [2/256] (Box 27)
    - Unknown - The Beardsley Limner - Clarendon Dix (1795) [2/265] (Box 27)
    - Unknown - Pair of Flemish Portrait Busts (1520) [1/79] (Box 27)
    - Unknown - La Fontaine's Fables [1/86] - The Cat and the Fox (Box 27)
    - Unknown - La Fontaine's Fables [1/86] - The Dog Who Dropped Substance for Shadow (Box 27)
    - Unknown - La Fontaine's Fables [1/86] - The Eagle and the Magpie (Box 27)
    - Unknown - La Fontaine's Fables [1/86] - The Heron (Box 27)
    - Unknown - La Fontaine's Fables [1/86] - The Lion (Box 27)
    - Unknown - La Fontaine's Fables [1/86] - The Lion and the Gnat (Box 27)
    - Unknown - Portrait of a Young Gentleman (1820) [1/97] (Box 27)
    - Unknown - Fish Arrow Weathervane [2/281] (Box 27)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Art Asian, African, Ancient, III_1_2_2
    - Acrobat, Man with Drum, Man Riding Haet'ae, Korea(1392-1910) [3/228] (Box 27)
    - African Antelope Headdress (Chi Wara) [3/403] (Box 27)
    - Asteas Neck Amphora [3/379] (Box 27)
    - The Bodhisattva Jizo, Japan Heian Period [3/233] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Pair of Boys Riding Qilin (1662-1722) [3/99] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Laozi Riding Water Buffalo, Ming (1368-1644) [3/90] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Seated Official, Ming (1368-1644) [3/86] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Dancing Lady, Tang (618-907) [3/77] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Jar, Han Dynasty (206 BC- 220 AD) [3/74] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Coverd Jar, Song (960-1127) [3/81] (Box 27)
    - Pair of Chinese Hexoganal Covered Vases (1662-1722) [3/93] (Box 27)
    - Egyptian Statuette of Anubis (332-30 BC) [3/371] (Box 27)
    - Haimon Painter Lekythos [3/376] (Box 27)
    - Haimon Painter Lekythos [3/377] (Box 27)
    - Isoda Koryusai - Cat Stalking Goldfish (1775) [3/326] (Box 27)
    - Isoda Koryusai - Courtesan Representing Jurojin (1772) [3/308] (Box 27)
    - Japanese Pheasant Incense Burner (Box 27)
    - Japanese Sleeping Cat (Box 27)
    - Krishna Gopis in Forest of Brindoban, India, 18th Century [3/211] (Box 27)
    - Komai Yoshinobu - Rabbits in Moonlight (1771) [3/327] (Box 27)
    - Nakayama Sugakudo - Un-mo no Niwatori Nebi-Ichigo (1858) [3/325] (Box 27)
    - Niwa Motokuni (Tokei) - Elaborately Caparisoned Horse Tethered to Tree (1820) [3/330] (Box 27)
    - One Handled Jug (AD 75-130) [3/385] (Box 27)
    - Paestum Group Squat Lekythos Painter of Palermo Lekythos [3/378] (Box 27)
    - Round Japanese Incense Burner [3/129] (Box 27)
    - Hexagonal Japanese Incense Burner [3/130] (Box 27)
    - Seated Tiger (1820) [3/328] (Box 27)
    - Scenes from the Life of Buddha, Nepal (1750) [3/215] (Box 27)
    - Suzuki Harunobu - Sotoba Komachi (1768) [3/307] (Box 27)
    - Swing Painter Amphora (530-520 BC) [3/375] (Box 27)
    - Syrian Incense Burner [3/391] (Box 27)
    - Unicorn and Deer, Nepal, 13th-14th Centuries [3/213] (Box 27)
    - Utagawa Hiroshige - Black-napped Oriole Perched on Stem of Rose Mallow (1835) [3/323] (Box 27)
    - Utagawa Hiroshige - Lion-Dog and Cub (Box 27)
    - Utagawa Hiroshige - Long Tailed Bird on Branch of Flowering Plumb (1838) [3/318] (Box 27)
    - Utagawa Hiroshige - Pheasant on Snow Clad Hillside (1832) [3/320] (Box 27)
    - Utagawa Hiroshige - Wagtail and Rose mallow (1840) [3/322] (Box 27)
    - Utagawa Kuniyoshi, Shizuka Gozen - Trudging Through Snow at Mt. Yoshino [3/333] (Box 27)
    - Utagawa Toyokuni II - Tiger and Bamboo (1825) [3/329] (Box 27)
    - Utagawa Toyohiro - Beauty Stepping into Ferry Boat [3/309] (Box 27)
    - Utagawa Yoshitsuya - Tiger, Peonies Waterfall (1861) [3/332] (Box 27)
    - Winterthur Group Hydra [3/383] and Como C Group Hydra [3/384] (Box 27)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Art, Unidentified, III_1_2_3
    - Art - Unidentified (Box 27)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Dishes, Porcelain, Metal, Glass, III_1_2_4
    - Bow - Candlesticks Modeled with Canaries (1765) [1/124] (Box 27)
    - Bow - Cock and Hen (1758) [4/90] (Box 27)
    - Bow - Fire and Water (1765) [4/38] (Box 27)
    - Bow - Flora Neptune (1755-60) [4/47] (Box 27)
    - Bow - Owl (1750-55) [4/90] (Box 27)
    - Bow - Rabbits (1755-1759) [4/79] (Box 27)
    - Bow - Sportsman and its Companion (1756-58) [4/60] (Box 27)
    - Chaimberlain's Worcester Set of Dinner and Soup Plates (1808-9) [1/187] (Box 27)
    - Chelsea - Actor and Actress in Turkish Costume (1760) [4/59] (Box 27)
    - Chelsea - Candlesticks with Hunting Groups (1760-69) [4/126] (Box 27)
    - Chelsea - Carp Tureen Cover (1755) [4/30] (Box 27)
    - Chelsea - Drum Bearer from Monkey Band (1753-65) [4/84] (Box 27)
    - Chelsea - Duck and Drake Tureens (1755) [4/23] (Box 27)
    - Chelsea - "Hans Sloane" Dishes (Box 27)
    - Chelsea - "Lady in the Pavilion" Teacups and Saucers (1749-52) [4/145] (Box 27)
    - Chelsea - Partridge Sauceboats and Covers (1755) [4/32] (Box 27)
    - Chelsea - Plaice Sauceboats, Covers, Ladles (1756) [4/29] (Box 27)
    - Chelsea - Porridge Plates (1755) [4/194] (Box 27)
    - Chelsea-Derby - Part Desert Service (1775) [4/196] (Box 27)
    - Chinese - 2 Bowls (1522-66) [3/84] (Box 27)
    - Chinese - Libation Cup (1662-1722) [3/91] (Box 27)
    - Chinese - Plate (1368-1644) [3/83] (Box 27)
    - Chinese - Square Dishes (1662-1722) [3/96] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Export - Candlesticks (1770) [4/128] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Export - Cup and Saucer (1770) [4/151] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Export - Cows (1800) [4/83] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Export - Dinner Service (1770) [4/277] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Export - Foxhunting Cylindrical Mug (1775) [4/152] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Export - Goose Tureen and Cover (1760-80) [4/36] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Export - Hares (1770-90) [4/83] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Export - "Rockefeller" Service (1790) [4/233] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Export - Seated Hounds (1770-80) [4/82] (Box 27)
    - Chinese Export - Spaniel (1750-70) [4/82] (Box 27)
    - Derby - Boars (1755-60) [4/81] (Box 27)
    - Derby - Dinner Service [4/190] (Box 27)
    - Derby - Dinner Service (1815) [4/203] (Box 27)
    - Derby - "Frill" Vases and Covers (1760) [4/131] (Box 27)
    - Derby - Garniture of 3 Crocus Vases and Covers (1790) [4/132] (Box 27)
    - English or Irish Lead Glass Finger Bowls (1780) [4/246] (Box 27)
    - Frankenthal Group of the Spanish Musicians (1765) [4/55] (Box 27)
    - Hochst Pair of Woodcock Tureens Covers (1750-55) [4/35] (Box 27)
    - Japanese - Various Dishes (Box 27)
    - Limbach Figure of Spring (1775-80) [4/43] (Box 27)
    - Longton Hall Strawberry Leaf Plates (1755) [4/144] (Box 27)
    - Ludwigsburg - Figures of Gardeners (1768-78) [4/73] (Box 27)
    - Ludwigsburg - Figure of Lady(1765) [4/53] (Box 27)
    - Hochst figure of a Sower (1780) [4/70] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Air and Fire (1745) [4/37] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Aqua Ground Circular Soup Bowl Set (1750) [4/147] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Bulgar (1745-50) [4/58] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Cook (1755-60) [4/66] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Cook (1745-50) and Lemon Seller (1755-60) [4/65] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Coppersmith (1750) [4/68] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Dessert Service (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Part Desert Service (1780) [4/156] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Dinner Plates (1755) [4/154] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Dinner Plates (1750) [4/154] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Four Season Candlesticks (1750-55) [4/40] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Fox with Chinese Export Fox (1745 and 1750-70) [4/75] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Italian Comedy Figures (1745) [4/56] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Leopards (1745-50) [4/74] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Miniature Animals (1745-50) [4/78] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Potter (1750) [4/69] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Sawyer and Woodcutter (1745-50) [4/64] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Sheep (1755-60) [4/77] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Sparrow Hawks (1735-40) [4/87] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Squirrel (1750) [4/76] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Sugar Casters and Covers (1750) [4/149] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Turks Holding Sweetmeat Bowls (1746) [4/137] (Box 27)
    - Meissen - Yellow Ground Chocolate Set (1745-50) [4/148] (Box 27)
    - Naples Set of Four Busts (1785) [4/63 (Box 27)
    - Paris - Dessert Plates (1810) [4/165] (Box 27)
    - Paris - Dessert Plates (1820) [4/167] (Box 27)
    - Paris - Dessert Service (1820) [4/166] (Box 27)
    - Paris - Part Dessert Service (1785) [4/164] (Box 27)
    - Pinxton - Dessert Service (1800) [4/214] (Box 27)
    - Pinxton - Dessert Service "Church Gresley" (1800-1810) [4/212] (Box 27)
    - Plymouth Four Continents Set (1768-70) [4/49] (Box 27)
    - Ralph Wood - Pastoral Group of the Flute Player (1770) [4/106] (Box 27)
    - Ralph Wood - The Vicar and Moses (1770) [4/107] (Box 27)
    - Silver - Candlesticks, Charles II (1670) [4/381] (Box 27)
    - Silver - Candlesticks, George I (1718) [4/390] (Box 27)
    - Silver - Coffee Pot, George II (1737) [4/399] (Box 27)
    - Silver - Deep Dishes, George II (1730) [4/396] (Box 27)
    - Silver - Dish, George II (1741) [4/402] (Box 27)
    - Silver - Jug, Charles II (1683) [4/382] (Box 27)
    - Silver - Pepper Casters, George I (1715-16) [4/389] (Box 27)
    - Silver - Sauce Boats, George II (1738) [4/399] (Box 27)
    - Silver - Tea Pot with Stand and Burner, Queen Anne (1712) [4/386] (Box 27)
    - Silver - Tray, George III (1793) [4/408] (Box 27)
    - Silver - Waiter, George II (1749) [4/402] (Box 27)
    - Spode - Dessert Service (1795-1815) [4/205] (Box 27)
    - Spode - Dessert Service (1810) [4/207] (Box 27)
    - Spode - Dessert Service (1815) [4/209] (Box 27)
    - Spode - Tea and Coffee Service (1820) [4/204] (Box 27)
    - Stafordshire, Probably Whieldon Agate Ware (1745) [4/98] (Box 27)
    - Strasbourg Cabbage Tureen and Stand (1754-60)[4/33] (Box 27)
    - Swansea Dessert Service (1820) [4/216] (Box 27)
    - Vienna Dessert Service (1812-13) [4/158] (Box 27)
    - Whieldon - Type - Milking Group (1760) [4/101] (Box 27)
    - Whieldon - Type - Ewe and Lamb (1755) [4/99] (Box 27)
    - Worchester "Dr. Syntax" Dessert Service (1820) [4/182] (Box 27)
    - Worchester and Chaimberlain's - Worchester Dinner Service (1788 1815) [4/186] (Box 27)
    - Worchester and Chaimberlain's - Worchester Dinner Service (1788 1815) [4/186] (Box 27)
    - Worchester Barr, Flight and Barr - Dessert Service (1807-13) [4/176] (Box 27)
    - Worchester Barr, Flight and Barr - Dessert Service (1810) [4/179] (Box 27)
    - Worchester Barr, Flight and Barr - Garniture of Three Vases (1808) [4/132] (Box 27)
    - Worchester Barr, Flight and Barr - Tea and Coffee Service (1807-1813) [4/175] (Box 27)
    - Worchester Barr, Flight and Barr - Tea and Coffee Service (1820) [4/184] (Box 27)
    - Worchester Barr, Flight and Barr - Teapot (1807-13) [4/175] (Box 27)
    - Worchester Dr. Wall - Dessert Service (1770) [4/169] (Box 27)
    - Worchester Dr. Wall - Quatrefoil, Baskets, Covers, Stands (1770) [4/139] (Box 27)
    - Worchester Dr. Wall - Quatrefoil Tureen (1770) (Box 27)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Dishes, Porcelain, Metal, Glass - Unidentified, III_1_2_5
    - Dishes, Porcelain, Metal, Glass - Unidentified (Box 27)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Furniture, III_1_2_6
    - Furniture (Box 27)
  - 8x10, Transparencies, Art A-Z, III_3_1_1
    - Manet, Edouard - The Brioche (1870) [1/115] (Box 28, Folder 81)
  - 8x10, Transparencies, Oriental Carpets/Rugs, III_3_1_2
    - Oriental Carpets/Rugs (Box 28, Folder 82)
  - 8x10, Transparencies, Dishes, III_3_1_3
    - Dishes (Box 28, Folder 83)
  - 8x10, Transparencies, Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden, III_3_1_4
    - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden - Moon Gate [3/20] (Box 28, Folder 84)
  - 8x10, Negatives, Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden, III_3_2_1
    - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden - Arhat Bhadra with Tiger Cub (1115-1234) [3/39] (Box 28, Folder 85)
    - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden - Buddhist Votive Stele (550-77) [3/31] (Box 28, Folder 85)
    - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden - Incense Burner (1644-1911) [3/44] (Box 28, Folder 85)
    - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden - Korean Sculptures of Military and Civil Officials [3/47] (Box 28, Folder 85)
    - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden - Moon Gate [3/26] (Box 28, Folder 85)
    - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden - Northern View [3/29] (Box 28, Folder 85)
    - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden - Octagonal Basin [3/61] (Box 28, Folder 85)
  - 8x10, Prints, Art A-Z, III_3_3_1
    - Baxter, John - Instruments at the Silence Factory (1960) [2/177] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Durer, Albrecht - The Elevation of St. Mary Magdalene (1501-4) [1/346] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Flemish Portrait Bust (1520) [1/79] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Gauguin, Paul - Maternite (1899) [1/195] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Gentilis, Vic - Something to Forget (1966) [1/334] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Hopper, Edward - Rich's House, North Truro (1930) [2/90] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Monet, Claude - Nympheas [1/143] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Monet, Claude - Nympheas (1918-21) [1/141] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Moore, Henry - Oval Sculpture (1964) [1/332] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Music, Antonio Zoran - Dalmatian Motif (1948) [1/324] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Picasso, Pablo - Girl with a Basket of Flowers (1905) [1/258] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Pissarro, Camille-Jacob - Shepherd and Church at Eragny (1889) [1/128] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Porzano, Giacomo - Brushes (1959) [1/327] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Redon, Odilon - Flowers [1/208] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Sheeler, Charles - White Sentinels (1942) [2/114] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - de Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri - Jane Avril (Le Cafe-Concert) (1893) [1/336] (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Vespignani, Renzo - Train (1947) [1/328] (Box 28, Folder 86)
  - 8x10, Prints, Art, Unidentified, III_3_3_2
    - Art - Unidentified (Box 28, Folder 87)
  - 8x10, Prints, Art, Asian, African, Native and Folk American, III_3_3_3
    - Arhat Bhadra with Tiger Cub (Chinese) [3/39] (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - Japanese Shrine (Zushi) [3/237] (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - Korean Man with Drum [3/228] (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - Korean Acrobat [3/228] (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - Korean Man Riding a Haet'ae [3/228] (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - Female Deity (Possibly Uma) (Thai) [3/220] (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - African Antelope Headdress (chi wara) [3/403] (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - Martinez, Maria - Sacred Meal Bowl (1925) [3/350] (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - Martinez, Maria - Jar (1926) [3/350] (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - Martinez, Maria - Vase (1925) [3/350] (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - Martinez, Maria - Vase (1926) [3/350] (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - Gilley, Wendell - Gaggle of Canada Geese (1971) [3/304] (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - American Eagle (1825) [3/275] (Box 28, Folder 88)
  - 8x10, Prints, Furniture, Dishes, Porecelain, III_3_3_4
    - Furniture, Dishes, Porcelain (Box 28, Folder 89)
  - 35mm, Negatives, Interiors at Seal Harbor, Maine, III_6_2_1
    - Interiors at Seal Harbor, Maine (Box 28, Folder 90)
- John D. Rockefeller, 3rd (JDR 3rd), IV
  - 4x5, Transparencies, Artwork, IV_1_1
    - Artwork (Box 29)
  - 4x5, Negatives, Museum Objects, IV_1_2
    - Museum Objects - Figurines - Animal/Human (Box 29)
    - Museum Objects - Paintings/Tapestries (Box 29)
    - Museum Objects - Plates/Flatware (Box 29)
    - Museum Objects - Vases, Urns, Bowls (Box 29)
    - Museum Objects - Miscellaneous (Box 29)
- Rodman C. Rockefeller (RCR), V
  - 4x5. Negatives, V_1_2
    - Portraiture (Box 29)
    - Busts (Box 29)
    - Painting (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 29)
  - 8x10, Transparencies, V_3_1
    - Paintings (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - 8x10, Prints, V_3_3
    - Paintings, Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 91)